Hello everyone. Welcome back to to this another new tutorial topic. So today we're going to
explore the update statement in the SQL, which allows us to modify the existing record in the
table. So first of all, this explanation for explain the SQL update statement. It is used to
modify the existing record in a table. It's a powerful tool for making change to the data.
And now just explore for how it works and use some example. Okay. So first of all, here, simply just
update the single record. Okay. So first of all, I can just select all open for the employees table
information. So first of all, here, I can just type select start and from here where I can just type
it is called the employees. Okay. Then create a semicolon and first of all, I can select and then execute.
Now you can see here the all the records of the employee stable. Okay.
So now just start for the first example, updating a single record. So open for another query and here
first type the update for the employees. So this one is the employee. And next step here, I can just
set for the h column is equal to so here. Different for the age is 35. Okay. And next step here,
I'll just type the while close use and perfectly just type here the first name. And
equal to so defined for the first name for here, the this one and also here use the end of
the portal and different for here the last name. So now just check for this table row and here
now here I can just insert for the last name of this one. So now just here type here, this is
completely typed for here the last name. So you can see here the updating the age column for the
employee's name, the Johan and 25 the query will modify now just select and execute. And you can
see here the Boolean condition. So now just check again. Okay. So here now not defined for the last
name. Okay. So here is a big mistake. So here I can insert for the last name. So declare for the
last name is equal to so here I can create perfectly now and then select all and then now for execute.
And you can say here perfectly to row is effective. So now just go here. You can see here the
age is 30. Now just I can execute. You can see here perfectly updated the age is 35. Okay.
So I hope you perfectly understand it. So next step here, I'll create for the updating the multiple
records. Okay. So you can see here now just go again. So here I can create for the update
employees and set for the department. Okay. So define for here the department column and now
here I can start for the wire to remove this and here use for the wire for the ages greater than
30. Okay. So you can see here and now just I can again select an execute and you can see
here the to row is completely affected. So again, I can just go here. Now I'll select an execute.
You can see here this perfectly defined for okay. So here I have mistakenly now defined for here.
So now here just again create for the department of the age. Okay.
So now just select all and then execute. You can see here perfectly affected
and just again select and verify in this stable information. And you can see here perfectly
changed for the department name for the age. Okay. So I hope you perfectly understand it.
And here I can completely update the department column for employees older than 30 to
age and this query will change the department of all employees age over the 35 to the age of
department. Okay. So the next step here I can create the updating report with the default value.
Okay. So you can destroy and go for again here. Create for the table name templates and then
I can just sit for the age. Okay. So define for the set of the age column
and here equal to just type for remove this. And here I'm going to create the
C O C O A L E. Then S E C. Okay. So this is perfect. And first of all, I'm going to create
the parentheses and in this insert I can define for the age column. And also I can define for the
age is 25. Okay. And now here I can only choose for the department. So now just department
choose. So here I can just type the department is equal to simply create for the single
quotation. And now here I can choose for the age is here. I can just select for define the age is
26 and then type for the department for the merge kitchen. So here is simply define and here
updating the age column for the employees. And here is the marketing department. And if
the employees is null and it will be updated for here using the coolest function. Okay. So now
first of all, select an execute. You can see here perfectly the one row is affected. Okay.
So now just go here. And then again for selecting this verification for the simplest table,
the next good, you can see here perfectly updated for now just change and here I can insert
for the age is 35. Okay. So now just here define for the age is 35.
And then again for select and execute. And perfectly affected, then just go again for check.
And verify you can see perfectly update for this statement.
So here this query will ensure the all employees in the department here, the department,
use the marketing you have and each assigned. So now here completely done for double view of the
update statement in the SQL with some practical example. Okay. So I hope you perfectly understand
this session. So thank you for watching and happy coding.